Guide to the Stan Steiner Papers, ca. 1940-1987 M0700
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series I. Subject Files
  - Politics -- Red Hunting
    - Walter-McCarran Immigration Act 1961 -1962 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Puerto Rico
    - The Addicts n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Alegria, Dr. Ricardo: Institute of Culture interview 1971 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Antilles n.d. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - The arts [1 of 2] 1971 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - The arts [2 of 2] 1971 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Army and Navy Bases n.d. (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Benitez, Jaime n.d. (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Betances n.d. (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Bi-Lingualism 1970 -1971 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Blacks and Slavery n.d. (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Borinquenos [1 of 4] n.d. (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Borinquenos [2 of 4] n.d. (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Borinquenos [3 of 4] n.d. (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Borinquenos [4 of 4] n.d. (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Business n.d. (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Caribbean Review n.d. (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Catholic Church n.d. (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Catholic University, Ponce 1971 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Chicago barrio n.d. (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Chicago barrio: El Puertoriquero n.d. (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Chicago barrio: The Rican n.d. (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Chicano / Puerto Rican Coalition n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Claridad.--Vol. 12, nos. 274 (1972 Sept. 20) and 284 (1970 Nov. 29) 1970 -1972 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Colonialism, Inc. n.d. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Commandos and Mira n.d. (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Commissioner Cordova Diaz n.d. (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Copper Mines of Utuado [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Copper Mines of Utuado [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - The Courts n.d. (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Crime and Police n.d. (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Culebra n.d. (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Drugs n.d. (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - East Harlem n.d. (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Economic Depression 1970 -1977[?] (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Education n.d. (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Education: Bilingualism n.d. (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Education: New York n.d. (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Environment n.d. (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Farm Workers 1967 -1972 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Farming n.d. (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Feliciano, Carlos: Nationalist Party and case n.d. (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Ferre, Governor Don Antonio [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Ferre, Governor Don Antonio [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Ferre, Governor Don Antonio n.d. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Fomento [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Fomento [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Geno's interview on Arts n.d. (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Health n.d. (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Hernandes Colon, Rafael n.d. (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - History: Grito de Lares 1971 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - History: Spanish Corner n.d. (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Hospital: Local 1199 1969 -1970 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Hospital: 1199 Drug & Hospital News.--Vol. 3, no. 6 1968 July (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Hospital: 1199 Drug & Hospital News.--Vol. 4, no. 8 1969 Sept. (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Hospital: 1199 Drug & Hospital News.--Vol. 4, no. 9 1969 Oct. (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Hospital: 1199 Drug & Hospital News.--Vol. 4, no. 10 1969 Nov. (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Hospital: 1199 Drug & Hospital News.--Vol. 5, no. 2 1970 Feb. (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Hospital: 1199 Drug & Hospital News.--Vol. 5, no. 4 1970 Apr. (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Hospital: 1199 Drug & Hospital News.--Vol. 5, no. 5 1970 May (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Hospital: 1199 Drug & Hospital News.--Vol. 5, no. 6 1970 June (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Hospital: 1199 Drug & Hospital News.--Vol. 5, no. 7 1970 July (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Hostos Community College [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Hostos Community College [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Housing and Urban Renewal, Tenants, and Squatters 1959 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - I.L.G.W.U. [International Ladies Garment Workers Union] n.d. (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - I.L.G.W.U. [International Ladies Garment Workers Union] n.d. (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Illinois: Spanish Speaking Study Committee n.d. (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Images n.d. (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Immigration n.d. (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Institute of Puerto Rican Culture n.d. (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Island Elections [1 of 2] 1972 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Island Elections [2 of 2] 1972 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Jibaros n.d. (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Jibaros: notes n.d. (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Jobs 1968 -1973 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Labor n.d. (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - L.A.D.O. [Latin American Defense Organiation] 1967 -1968 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - La Marcha and Governor's Conference n.d. (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - The Land -- Squatters and Agrenados 1971 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Latino -- 2nd ed. Aug-Sept, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Law and Prisons n.d. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Lincoln Hospital n.d. (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Loiza River n.d. (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Los Indios n.d. (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Machismo n.d. (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Mari Bras n.d. (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Migration Division 1968-1973 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Movimiento por Independencia --MPI n.d. (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - MPI n.d. (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Múñoz Marín n.d. (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Northeast Neighbors Association, Lower East Side [1 of 3] 1969 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Northeast Neighbors Association, Lower East Side [2 of 3] 1969 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Northeast Neighbors Association, Lower East Side [3 of 3] 1969 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - North/South Center n.d. (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - NPP n.d. (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - On the Bench of Cleveland 1971 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Petroleum n.d. (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - PIP 1971 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - The Polar Bear Club n.d. (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - The Police n.d. (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Politics in USA: Communists n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Politics in USA: Reform Democrats and Badillo n.d. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Ponce Massacre and Albiro Campos and the Nationalists n.d. (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Populares n.d. (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - PRIDCO [Puerto Rico Industrial Development Company] n.d. (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - PRIDCO Strike 1970 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Protestant Churches n.d. (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Puerto Rican Forum [1 of 2] 1968 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Puerto Rican Forum [2 of 2] 1968 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Puerto Rican Socialist Party n.d. (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Puerto Rican Student Union n.d. (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Puerto Rican Stuff To Be Translated n.d. (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Puerto Rico Maps n.d. (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - San Juan n.d. (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Santiago Vásquez, Antonio n.d. (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Schools 1970 Dec 6 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Shopping Centers n.d. (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Songs and Music 1971 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Songs of Roy Brown n.d. (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - South Bronx 1970-1973 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Spiritualism n.d. (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Squatters n.d. (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Squatters and Urban Renewal MHC [1 of 3] n.d. (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Squatters and Urban Renewal MHC [2 of 3] n.d. (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Squatters and Urban Renewal MHC [3 of 3] n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - St. Mark's of the Bowery n.d. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Statistics: Puerto Rican Population in New York City; Columbia University 1954 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Sugar n.d. (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Solar Favale, Santiago n.d. (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Theatre of the Streets n.d. (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - The Theatre of the Streets n.d. (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Toa Vaca n.d. (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Tourists n.d. (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Traffic Highways and Cars n.d. (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - University of Puerto Rico n.d. (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Utuado: Matos, Don Pedro 1971-1972 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Vieques n.d. (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Water Resources n.d. (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Welfare n.d. (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Women n.d. (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Women -- The Island n.d. (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Writers & Poets -- New York n.d. (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Yauco Pipeline n.d. (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Young Lords n.d. (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Young Lords Conference 1970 Sept 22-23 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Young Lords on Island 1971 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Young Women in the Barrios n.d. (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Youth & Student Movements n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Mar. 11 [1971 University of Puerto Rico Student Riots] 1971 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous n.d. (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Religion
    - American Council of Christian Laymen n.d. (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - American Public Relations Forum n.d. (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Catholic Church 1970 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Christian Anti-Communist Crusade n.d. (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Christian National Crusade n.d. (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - The Evangelists n.d. (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Free Speech Association n.d. (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Freedom School n.d. (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Jewish Organizations -- Promotion n.d. (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - The Mormons 1985 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Mexican-Indian Religions and Relations 1967 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - National Federation of Christian Laymen n.d. (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Penitentes n.d. (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Religion: The Catholic Church 1942-1958 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Religion: The Jews n.d. (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Religion: The Protestants 1944-1958 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Religion: In Socialist Nations 1943-1958 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Soviet Culture
    - Culture Exchanges: USA - USSR 1955-1959 Dec 10 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Culture Exchanges: USA - USSR: Interviews, Et. Al. n.d. (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Pre-Revolutionary Russian Culture and Arts 1941-1946 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Soviet Art 1957-1958 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Soviet Ballet 1956 Mar. 30-1959 Ap4.26, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Soviet Folk Ballet 1958 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Soviet Films 1946 Mar. 25-1958 Oct. 22 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Soviet Literature: 1917-1930 1946 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Soviet Literature: War Years 1943-1945 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Soviet Literature: Contemporary 1945-1958 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Case of Dr. Zhivago 1957-1958 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Soviet Music 1943 Oct. -1957 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Soviet Theatre 1943 May 1-1958 Apr. 16, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Urbanism
    - The City Life Styles [includes TMs, 4 pp] c. 1970 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Civil Rights n.d. (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Housing 1967 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Los Angeles Blowout 1968 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - New York and Telephone Pole 1974 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Racism n.d. (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Urban Peasants n.d. (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Urban Youth 1967 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Women
    - Adoption and Sale of Children 1955-1959 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Birth Control 1940-1950 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Birth Control on Islands [Puerto Rico] n.d. (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Economics: Working Women 1939-1958 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - John-Steiner, Vera, Ph.D: Nominee for the Wonder Woman Foundation Awards 1983 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Marriage: Illegitimacy n.d. (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Marriage: Traditional n.d. (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Marriage: Youth c. 1958 (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Marriage and Divorce n.d. (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Prostitution: The Laws 1958-1959 (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - Prostitution: The Women c. 1959 (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - Prostitution 1967 (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - Venereal Diseases n.d. (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - Women of the West n.d. (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - Women of the West [includes: Barker, Elliott S. "A Tribute to My Pioneer Mother Priscilla Jane Barker," TMs] n.d. (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - [Women and Women's Liberation] [1 of 5] c. 1945-1976 (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - [Women and Women's Liberation] [2 of 5] c. 1945-1976 (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - [Women and Women's Liberation] [3 of 5] c. 1945-1976 (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - [Women and Women's Liberation] [4 of 5] c. 1945-1976 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - [Women and Women's Liberation] [5 of 5] [Includes: Vera John-Steiner and Patricia Irvine, "Women's Verbal Images & Associations" TMs, 12 pp.] c. 1945-1976 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Youth
    - American Youth for Democracy 1943 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Jewish Youth 1943 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - NAACP Youth Councils 1947-1948 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Negro Youth 1948 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Negro Youth: Jim Crow 1944 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Rural Youth 1966 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Southern Negro Youth 1948 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - SSOC: Southern Student Organizing COmmittee 1967-1968 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Protestant Church Youth 1943-1947 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Veterans 1947 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Young Communist League 1943 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Young for Christ 1943-1945 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Young Progressives 1948 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Miscellany
    - Adobe n.d. (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Association of American Physicians and Surgeons n.d. (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Book Publishing n.d. (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Camping n.d. (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Early Sketches n.d. (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Family and Personal Stuff n.d. (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Intermountain Tucson Base, CIA n.d. (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Memorabilia of Lockett and Patterson Families 1860-1919? (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Foreign Currency n.d. (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Health n.d. (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Institute of Noetic Sciences n.d. (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Map of House n.d. (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - The Mechanical Language n.d. (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - Memoirs of Hungary [1 of 2] 1979 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Memoirs of Hungary [2 of 2] [includes: Veronika P. Steiner, "Detente on the Danube," TMs, 6 pp] 1979 (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Memoirs of Hungary: photos n.d. (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - Nixoniana n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Peace Groups 1967 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Postage Stamp Collection n.d. (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Science n.d. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Steineriana n.d. (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Western Writers of America n.d. (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - WWA logo n.d. (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Xerox Xerox Xerox n.d. (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Untitled [Nudist Magazines] n.d. (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Series II. Correspondence
  - Chronological
    - Letters 1945 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Letters 1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Letters 1961 Jan. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Letters 1961 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Letters 1961 Mar. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Letters 1961 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Letters 1961 May (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Letters 1961 June (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Letters 1961 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Letters 1961 Oct. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Letters 1961 Nov. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Letters 1962 Jan. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Letters 1962 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Letters 1962 Mar. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Letters 1962 May (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Letters 1962 June (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Letters 1962 July (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Letters 1962 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Letters 1962 Sept. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Letters 1962 Oct. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Letters 1962 Nov. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Letters 1962 Dec. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Letters 1963 Jan. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Letters 1963 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Letters 1963 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Letters 1963 May (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Letters 1963 June (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Letters 1963 July (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Letters 1963 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Letters 1963 Sept. (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Letters 1963 Oct. (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Letters 1963 Nov. (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Letters 1963 Dec. (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Letters 1964 Jan. [?] (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Letters 1964 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Letters 1964 Mar. (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Letters 1964 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Letters 1964 May (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Letters 1964 June (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Letters 1964 July (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Letters 1964 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Letters 1964 Sept. (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Letters 1964 Oct. (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Letters 1964 Nov. (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Letters 1964 Dec. (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Letters 1965 Jan. (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Letters 1965 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Letters 1965 Mar. (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Letters 1965 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Letters 1965 May (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Letters 1965 June (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Letters 1965 July (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Letters 1965 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Letters 1965 Sept. (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Letters 1965 Oct. (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Letters 1965 Nov. (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Letters 1965 Dec. (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Letters 1966 Jan. (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Letters 1966 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Letters 1966 Mar. (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Letters 1966 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Letters 1966 May (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Letters 1966 June (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Letters 1966 July (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Letters 1966 Aug. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Letters 1966 Sept. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Letters 1966 Oct. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Letters 1966 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Letters 1966 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Letters 1967 Jan. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Letters 1967 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Letters 1967 Mar. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Letters 1967 Apr. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Letters 1967 May (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Letters 1967 June (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Letters 1967 July (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Letters 1967 Aug. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Letters 1967 Sept. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Letters 1967 Oct. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Letters 1967 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Letters 1967 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Letters 1968 Jan. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Letters 1968 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Letters 1968 Mar. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Letters 1968 Apr. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Letters 1968 May (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Letters 1968 June (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Letters 1968 July (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Letters 1968 Aug. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Letters 1968 Sept. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Letters 1968 Oct. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Letters 1968 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Letters 1968 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Letters 1969 Jan. (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Letters 1969 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Letters 1969 Mar. (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Letters 1969 Apr. (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Letters 1969 May (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Letters 1969 June (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Letters 1969 July (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Letters 1969 Aug. (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Letters 1969 Sept. (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Letters 1969 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Letters 1969 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Letters 1970 Jan. (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Letters 1970 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Letters 1970 Mar. (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Letters 1970 Apr. (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Letters 1970 May (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Letters 1970 June (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Letters 1970 July (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Letters 1970 Aug. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Letters 1970 Sept. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Letters 1970 Oct. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Letters 1970 Nov. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Letters 1970 Dec. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Letters 1971 Jan. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Letters 1971 Feb. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Letters 1971 Mar. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Letters 1971 Apr. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Letters 1971 May (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Letters 1971 June (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Letters 1971 July (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Letters 1971 Aug. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Letters 1971 Sept. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Letters 1971 Oct. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Letters 1971 Nov. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Letters 1971 Dec. (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Letters 1972 Jan. (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Letters 1972 Feb. (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Letters 1972 Mar. (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Letters 1972 Apr. (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Letters 1972 May (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Letters 1972 June (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Letters 1972 July (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Letters 1972 Aug. (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Letters 1972 Sept. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Letters 1972 Oct. (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Letters 1972 Nov. (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Letters 1972 Dec. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Letters 1973 Jan. (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Letters 1973 Feb. (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Letters 1973 Mar. (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Letters 1973 Apr. (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Letters 1973 May (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Letters 1973 June (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Letters 1973 July (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Letters 1973 Aug. (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Letters 1973 Sept. (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Letters 1973 Oct. (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Letters 1973 Nov. (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Letters 1973 Dec. (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Letters 1974 Jan. (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Letters 1974 Feb. (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Letters 1974 Mar. (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Letters 1974 Apr. (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Letters 1974 May (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Letters 1974 June (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Letters 1974 July (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Letters 1974 Aug. (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Letters 1974 Sept. (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Letters 1974 Oct. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Letters 1974 Nov. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Letters 1974 Dec. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Letters 1975 Jan. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Letters 1975 Feb. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Letters 1975 Mar. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Letters 1975 Apr. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Letters 1975 May (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Letters 1975 June (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Letters 1975 July (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Letters 1975 Aug. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Letters 1975 Sept. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Letters 1975 Oct. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Letters 1975 Nov. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Letters 1975 Dec. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Letters 1976 Jan. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Letters 1976 Feb. (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Letters 1976 Mar. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Letters 1976 Apr. (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Letters 1976 May (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Letters 1976 June (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Letters 1976 July (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Letters 1976 Aug. (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Letters 1976 Sept. (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Letters 1976 Oct. (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Letters 1976 Nov. (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Letters 1976 Dec. (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Letters 1977 Jan. (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Letters 1977 Feb. (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Letters 1977 Mar. (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Letters 1977 Apr. (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Letters 1977 May (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Letters 1977 June (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Letters 1977 July (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Letters 1977 Aug. (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Letters 1977 Sept. (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Letters 1977 Oct. (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Letters 1977 Nov. (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Letters 1977 Dec. (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Letters 1978 Jan. (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Letters 1978 Feb. (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Letters 1978 Mar. (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Letters 1978 Apr. (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Letters 1978 May (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Letters 1978 June (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Letters 1978 July (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Letters 1978 Aug. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Letters 1978 Sept. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Letters 1978 Oct. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Letters 1978 Nov. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Letters 1978 Dec. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Letters 1979 Jan. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Letters 1979 Feb. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Letters 1979 Mar. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Letters 1979 Apr. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Letters 1979 May (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Letters 1979 June (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Letters 1979 July (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Letters 1979 Aug. (Box 5, Folder 13)